<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>El-notes on Notes</title>
    <link>/el-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in El-notes on Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/el-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/el-notes/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/readme/</guid>
      <description>EL Notes If you want, please compile all statistics and data you find in this repository. For EL4131. Additional articles are also appreciated.
Directory Structure ├── Archive │ ├── _index.m │ ├── Stats and Quotes Notes (as of 191021) │ └── Data and Stats (as of 220921 0014) ├── Stats and Quotes Notes.m ├── Crime and Punishment │ ├── _index.m │ ├── Crime and Punishment.m │ ├── Stanford Prison Experiment │ │ ├── _index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stats and Quotes Notes</title>
      <link>/el-notes/stats-and-quotes-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/el-notes/stats-and-quotes-notes/</guid>
      <description>Stats and Quotes Notes Table of Contents  Stats and Quotes Notes  Table of Contents Science  Examples  Medicine and Pharmacology Ethics Genetic Engineering Inequality and Discrimination Peer-Review Processes in Research   Stats  COVID-19 Vaccination Inequality and Discrimination Medicine and Pharmacology     Technology  Definitions  Cancel Culture Big Tech AI Surveillence and Security   Quotes  Cancel Culture Morals and Ethics   Examples  Social Media Big Tech Cancel Culture Prejudice and Discrimination AI  Autonomous Vehicles     Stats  Social Media Autonomous Vehicles Big Tech and Big Data Cancel Culture Surveillance Security   Morals and Ethics Youth  Tech Talent Crunch AI     Prejudice and Discrimination  Examples Stats  Women in Tech Meritocracy &amp;amp; Elitism     Crime and Punishment  Examples   China  Quotes Stats   Hybrid Workplaces Inequalty     Science Examples Medicine and Pharmacology  The National Heart Centre Singapore has proposed that scans of patients’ hearts could be turned into 3D models.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
